[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
THE GRAVITY OF BEING A LAND DWELLER
- [growls]
- [gasps]
Keep your mitts off my grandson!
[yells in pain]
[rock music playing]
- Damn you!
- [both grunt]
Mmm. [laughs]
That reminds me.
I still haven't made my point, Legoshi.
You see, there's a little bit more
to that policy of mine
I'm always yammering on about.
Pacifism on its own
is an honorable choice in life,
but you'll come to learn
it only becomes meaningful
when it's advocated by the strong.
[all grunt]
[eagles groan]
- [yells]
- [Gosha grunts]
- Mmm.
- Huh?
- [laughs]
- [metal clanking]
- [yells]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- [metal clanks]
Huh?
You want to put
this punk ass down, Legoshi?
- Huh? "Put him down"?
- [eagle gagging]
[Legoshi grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
Those birds are flyers,
so they're naturally lightweight.
Not exactly built for a brawl like this.
You make a solid point.
You must have been
in your fair share of fights.
[splutters] No, not at all.
I just read it somewhere.
[laughs]
Well, either way, these chumps just got
their asses handed to 'em by an old man.
They'll wake up soon enough.
[Gosha grunts softly]
- Listen, kiddo.
- [Legoshi] Mmm?
Only reason I stopped by
is 'cause I was worried about you.
But it looks to me like
you no longer need any help from Grandpa.
[both chuckle softly]
[music ends]
[Louis] Azuki, I do hope that
you enjoyed the wine this evening.
I did, Louis.
And I would swear I saw a hint of a smile
after you tasted that tagliolini.
Yes. How could I not, with the asparagus
in that buttery cream sauce?
A truly elegant dish.
You really do have
a regular appetite then.
[Louis] Hmm?
Forgive me for asking,
but my father, he mentioned to me
that you had lost your right leg.
Ah, yes.
There was an accident.
Truth be told,
I'm very fortunate to be alive right now.
Oh, is that so?
Mmm. This accident didn't impact you
sexually, did it?
Excuse me?
Well, it's very important that I know.
If we were to marry and learn later
that we couldn't have children,
we'd be in real trouble.
[Louis huffs]
I'll have you know
that The Horns Conglomerate
is not so desperate
that I'd answer that question
in a place like this.
[giggles] For all your worldliness,
you're still so naive.
[Louis grunts softly]
Though maybe
I should've followed your lead
and made my invitation
a little more charming and direct.
I booked us a room.
[Louis hesitates]
I mean, we are going to be married
after all.
We might as well
get to know each other properly.
[gasps]
- [Louis grunting softly]
- [Azuki moaning]
- Azuki, wait.
- Mmm, what's the matter?
- Are you not enjoying this?
- No, it's just...
- Could you get me a glass of water?
- [giggles]
[Louis] I'm acting like a virgin.
What's wrong with me?
The very fact that carnivores
and herbivores coexist in the same society
is an affront to the laws of nature.
- [goat] You have to admit that.
- [sheep] Isn't that a rather extreme view?
[sheep] Now, I don't believe
that society would've developed as it has
if carnivores and herbivores
hadn't chosen to live together.
[goat] And if we lived separately,
we wouldn't see the awful devouring...
[Louis] Is this really okay?
The consummation
of a marriage of convenience?
Is this really meant to be my purpose?
[TV conversation continues]
[Ibuki] Louis, you changed my life
for the better.
[Azuki moaning softly]
[Louis] It's fine. This is fine.
Fragile, slender bodies coming together.
This is normal. Nothing strange about it.
I'm the one who's become strange.
Everything about this situation
feels so out of place.
[TV conversation continues indistinctly]
Her kiss isn't like Juno's.
The sensation of those hard canine teeth
isn't there.
[both grunt]
No, stop comparing them! Concentrate!
Don't get distracted.
Stay on the right path.
Make love to her.
It's as simple as that. Do it!
Make love to Azuki,
a female of your own species!
- Uh... Huh?
- [goat on TV] It's dangerous, abnormal!
[strained groaning]
Louis, are you all right?
[gags]
- [retching]
- [Azuki gasps]
[Louis coughs]
[Louis] There's no question now.
I'm no longer who I used to be.
FESTIVAL OF THE METEOR
JULY 27, FRIDAY
[Mayor] Hmm.
This one isn't half bad either.
MAYOR
[sniffs]
[sighs contentedly]
- [cell phone buzzing]
- Huh?
[sighs]
[groans]
Hey. I thought I told you not to call.
[Doku-Gumi crew] What,
did you forget about our agreement?
Why is that damn horse
still strutting around on the streets
at night like he owns the place?
Well?
All right, take it easy.
Go sunbathing or whatever it is
you reptiles do to pass the time.
It's all taken care of.
[slurps, gulps]
Mmm.
[eagles groaning, panting]
- [eagle 3] Are you okay, man?
- [eagle 1 grunts]
What was with those guys?
That shit was nuts.
Hey, toss me one of those.
[grunts]
[drink fizzes]
Yo, give me some of that.
You're the one who got us into this mess
in the first place!
Hey!
- [grunts]
- [chokes]
[high-pitched] I didn't mean anything
by it! Come on!
- Hey, let's calm down.
- [both grunt, groan]
- [burps softly, sighs]
- [can clanks]
[gasps]
[eagle 1 laughing maniacally]
[yelps]
Hmm.
- Goddamn embarrassing.
- [both shudder]
One can of Kines and that buddy of yours
kicked both your asses this bad?
No, that's not it.
All this is from that old geezer.
- Geezer?
- Yeah, some crazy old lizard guy.
That freaky-ass, venomous old fart.
[Yahya] Venomous?
It couldn't be. Is it really you?
After all these years,
why would you show yourself now?
You chose to betray me,
and you turned your back on the world.
36 YEARS EARLIER
- [engines revving]
- [Yahya] Hey, wait up!
Just take the damn thing, would you?
[upbeat music playing]
Don't just toss it around!
This is all so stupid.
Why was I the only one to get a medal?
You were the one who noticed the fire
in the first place, right?
If I were alone, there's no way
I ever could've saved that kid.
How's that supposed to be fair?
Don't get mad. That's just how it is.
In that case, "how it is" can kiss my ass.
[Gosha gasps]
- [gasps]
- Ha!
I should have done that
right from the start.
Fancy medals like that,
they're not really our thing, pal.
[Yahya] When I was young, I truly believed
that I could move forward
without ever looking back
because I had you,
a partner who could make
my 350-degree vision a perfect circle.
Hey, Gosha! We're going to change
this screwed up world!
You and me, together!
Together, there was nothing
we couldn't do.
Back then, neither Gosha nor I
dreamt of becoming the Beastar.
No, we wanted to be Beastars as a team.
[music ends]
But that night,
everything changed forever.
[jaguar chuckles]
You've got great fur.
It's going to make me some money.
But, you know, I think I'll start
by removing your fangs.
And don't you worry, darling,
you'll sleep through the whole thing.
[gasps, grunts]
[choking]
[exhales]
[thuds]
Looks like we made it just in time.
[gasps]
- [chiming]
- [soft music playing]
[Toki gasps softly]
[Toki] Your scales...
They're shiny like jewels.
You're so pretty.
Huh?
Hmm. Huh?
[soft music continues]
[music ends]
[Toki] Um, thank you for saving me.
There's been a rash of these sorts
of incidents in recent days.
Beasts are being drugged
with sleeping pills and skinned alive.
You got to be careful out there.
I see. So that's what this was.
I suppose I was almost
turned into a fur coat, huh?
[Yahya] Within 24 hours,
she and Gosha were dating.
And what's more...
SIX MONTHS LATER
...to my surprise, it lasted.
A lizard and a wolf, huh?
Man, talk about your unlikely
interspecies couples.
[mysterious music playing]
Do you even share the same values?
If we didn't share those, we never
would've made it through six months.
[Yahya sighs]
So, you wanted to talk?
Uh, I did, yeah.
I just found out that my girl's pregnant.
What?
The kid is mine.
Huh? [splutters] Who's the father?
I just told you. I'm the father.
Yeah, yeah, but...
You're oviparous, she's viviparous.
You shouldn't be able to get her pregnant.
The doctor said it was a miracle baby.
I have to support her.
[splutters] You're joking, right?
That delivery will be too risky,
and you know it.
Hey. Listen.
We were just getting started.
This is no time
to run off and start a family.
I mean, like...
We still have to become Beastars together
and fix the world.
[Gosha sighs]
- Not me, I'm done.
- [gasps]
[Gosha grunts, groans]
I thought that if we became Beastars,
it would be a win
for peace and coexistence.
But then, I found her, and I realized
she's the most important thing to me.
[sighs] So you're saying
you're going to leave me on my own.
[Gosha sighs]
[Yahya] You traitor.
[music ends]
- [device ringing]
- Huh.
[mouse beeps]
I've been looking into that wolf case,
and I got an update.
I'm listening.
It seems like
his parents are out of the picture,
and his high school records
list his grandfather as his guardian.
And wait till you get a load of this.
That grandfather is a Komodo dragon.
[Yahya] His eyes, those eyebrows...
Huh. There really is a family resemblance.
Guess we need to dangle a carrot
and lure the kid in.
[Corne] Done and done.
UDON BEBEBE
[Legoshi reading] "I'm in trouble.
I need your advice. Bill."
- What could have happened?
- [Sunaga] Hey, Legoshi.
- Uh, yes?
- I've been thinking.
It's time for you to try making a delivery
to one of our aquatic customers.
Would you define "aquatic"?
I want you to deliver an order
to a customer who is an ocean creature.
Oh. Oh, yeah, one of them.
Yeah, that makes sense. Uh, "deliver"?
Our motto at this humble restaurant is,
"We serve all species."
Just tell them you're from Udon Bebebe.
They'll get it.
Uh, hold on,
they speak ocean language, right?
[splutters] I'm not familiar with it,
so, uh...
Oh, Legoshi, you're a Cherryton student.
It'll be no problem for you.
"Apupupoupi bebebe berobu ponporopoo."
That's the only thing you have to say.
Huh? Okay, one more time.
Uh, pep-pop, poo--
You sure I should go?
MARINE ZONE THREE
Hmm.
Let's see here.
Number four.
Hmm, this should be it.
[heavy clunking]
- Then... I'm supposed to ring this?
- [dinging]
[funky music playing]
Okay.
Hmm.
Okay, when we first make eye contact,
I say, "Bogora bogora."
[Legoshi gasps]
[splutters nervously] Bogora bogora.
[speaking ocean language]
[sighs] Oh, man, what do I do? What do I--
Uh, I brought you Bebebe udon.
You know, udon.
- Udon? Udon? I brought it for you?
- [fish speaks indistinctly]
You placed an order with us,
dear customer.
And I brought it-- Ow!
[gasps] Valued customer,
my finger is not a noodle. I--
Please let go.
[splutters in ocean language]
- [seal in English] Don't panic.
- [gasps] Huh?
[seal] Ocean creatures,
they see movement, they try to eat.
It's normal.
Just stay still and they'll let you go.
Uh... I don't...
Allow me to interpret for you.
It'll go a lot easier.
[speaking in ocean language]
[Legoshi] That's right.
Seals are half land, half sea creatures.
- [chuckles]
- Hmm.
This bilingual guy just saved my fur.
[speaking ocean language]
[seal] He says, "I eat my udon."
[Legoshi] Right. Here you are.
[squeals, burps]
[Legoshi] Hmm?
Wait, what about the bill?
That bowlful of seashells becomes cash.
- Take it to the exchange.
- The exchange?
Seashells are the currency of the sea.
They are valuable little things.
Ah. I think I remember learning that.
Uh...
Seriously, thank you so much.
You really, uh... You really helped me out.
I am what you call a spotted seal.
My name is Sagwan.
You and I,
we live in the same apartment building,
so we help each other out.
Huh? You're in Beast Apartments?
[Legoshi] That's incredible.
Six months ago,
I was still living at home in the ocean.
Now, I work, teaching the ocean language
at a big university,
as I continue to study
the ways of the land.
[Legoshi] Mmm.
The land, I think it's a lovely place.
And I do quite like--
- [groaning]
- Are you all right?
You've got to keep an eye out
when you're wandering around like that.
The land can be really dangerous.
It's okay, I'm good.
The ocean's no different.
Uh, well, I guess
that's probably true, but...
And besides, if I am to die, that's just
the way things are meant to go that day.
- [grunts softly]
- What?
[Sagwan] In the ocean,
a big fish will eat the smaller fish.
And then, a bigger fish
will come and eat that big fish.
Then, eventually,
that bigger fish will die.
Then all the tiny fish and plankton
come to eat that.
All the creatures of the sea,
we must eat and we must be eaten.
We must eat and we must be eaten.
This is how we're all connected.
Down there,
the word "devouring" does not exist.
This is the harmony
that everybody lives within.
"They must eat and they must be eaten."
Yet you're telling me
they live in harmony?
Whoa. [gasps]
I can't imagine that such a world exists.
Here I am, tormented by my instincts,
trying to relate to herbivores,
when right next to me,
there's another world.
Hmm.
[Sagwan] My apartment is number 501.
Would you like to have some tea?
I still want to hear your story too.
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Hmm.
- [knocks]
- [Sagwan] Come in!
Thank you for-- Whoa! No!
Legoshi, is everything all right?
Uh, not exactly.
Uh, you... you got to put that away.
[spluttering] I mean, please wear clothes.
On land, you can't just be naked
around other people.
Oh, good to know.
Well, I'll put clothes on.
Please forgive me for any impoliteness.
Wait, hold on.
Hmm?
I can't just impose my beliefs on him
in his own room, right?
You must find clothes uncomfortable,
Mr. Sagwan.
You're welcome to stay as you are.
[chiming lightly]
[Legoshi] "Eat and be eaten,"
but everyone still lives in harmony.
I just can't wrap my head around it.
Here on land,
everyone's afraid of each other.
Carnivores and herbivores
try so hard to keep their distance.
[Sagwan] Legoshi.
Did you experience
some kind of trouble, perhaps?
There was a rumor
that a wolf with a devouring record
moved into our building.
Apartment gossip, I would say.
But was that you?
Hmm, so there were rumors, huh?
Back in the ocean, I was a carnivore too,
just like you, Legoshi.
In the ocean, everybody learns
how to live with their sins.
Doesn't that weigh on you?
It is not so heavy.
When I look at this,
it feels like I'm floating in the sea.
[chiming lightly]
The balance is kept
because they are all connected.
[Legoshi] Whoa.
When I'm with this person, it...
it's like I'm conversing
with the ocean itself.
It feels as if I'm floating, weightless.
I think... I kind of like this guy.
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪